joomagic.com 2015-05-09

# Privacy Policy - Joomla Template - Joomagic

JooMagic.com is dedicated to preserving the privacy of all of our customers.  JooMagic recognizes that our customers have valid concerns about how the personal information that they submit online will be used, and we pledge to provide the safest online environment possible. Keep reading to find out how our commitment to privacy benefits you.

In order to ensure that we are in compliance with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA), we have established this Privacy Commitment and have designated a Privacy Officer to oversee its implementation.

## Types of Information We Collect and Store

Information we have received from you through your registration or through your requests for information is limited to your name, username, country of residence and email address. Any other information you may provide to us is on a voluntary basis. 

We maintain a record of each of our members under carefully controlled conditions to ensure it cannot be accessed by unauthorized persons. Welimit the required information we collect to the absolute minimum necessary to us to contact you as outlined above. If you no longer wish to receive notification from ICPM or other project management productsand services, or to file a privacy complaint, please contact us.

Information is collected to let us e-mail you periodically to keep youaware of upcoming activities, partnerships and promotions.

## Non-Members That Are Browsing Our Content

Some of the content found on our websites is available for anyone to read at their leisure. JooMagic does not collect personal information from customers who are simply visiting one of our websites. If you visited our website by clicking on a link from one of our affiliates, it is possible a cookie was placed on your machine by the affiliate tracking software. The only purpose of this cookie is to note that you were referred to us by an affiliate so that the affiliate can receive a commission payment if you buy something.

## Registered Members

Much of our content can be viewed by people that register with us as "Members". Visitors are not required to become registered Members, but we do offer incentives to register and we request a minimum amount of information. Your registration information is stored in a secure database for use by JooMagic and our affiliates. Your personal information will never be shared with or sold to a third party. Members will automatically be signed up to receive our occassional newsletter. Each newsletter will contain a link to unsubscribe at any time.

## Downloads and Requested Information

When you request information from JooMagic about products or services, you must release a minimal amount of information (such as name, email address, etc.).  This information, along with your original request, is stored in a secure database for use by JooMagic or our affiliates only. Your personal information will never be shared with or sold to a third party. 

JooMagic occasionally sends out emails with special announcements, offers, or updates.  If it is determined that one of these emails is applicable to your earlier request and may benefit you, JooMagic will send you the email. If you would prefer not to receive these emails, you can have your name removed from our mailing list.

## Customers That Have Made a Purchase

When you request information from JooMagic about products or services, you must release a minimal amount of information (such as name, email address, etc.).  This information, along with your original request, is stored in a secure database for use by JooMagic or our affiliates only. Your personal information will never be shared with or sold to a third party. We maintain this information for a number of purposes.

  * In the event that a customer loses his or her username and/or password (where applicable), we will use our database to verify that customer’s purchase and retrieve his or her information.
  * JooMagic occasionally sends out emails with special announcements, offers, or updates.  If you would prefer not to receive these emails, you can have your name removed from our mailing list.
  * JooMagic will also send an email before your license is due to expire to tell you how much you will owe to renew your license (where applicable).

JooMagic understands that our customers are concerned about the privacy of their credit card information when making purchases online.  For that reason, we use a secure third-party credit card processing site.  The information you provide on this site will remain strictly confidential and will not be used for any unauthorized purpose.  It will not be shared with any third parties.

Our email list will not be sold to or shared with any third parties. You may remove your name from this list at any time by clicking on a link at the bottom of the email (this link appears in every email)

The JooMagic.com website(s) contain some links to third-party sites.  JooMagic has no control over these sites.  These sites have their own privacy policies and customers who visit these sites should become familiar with them.

JooMagic values our customers and takes the privacy concerns of our customers seriously.  If you have any further questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

* * *
